Finding Aid for the Bill Kovach Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Bill Kovach Papers
undated
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0783
23.75 linear_feet
- Calendars, 1979-1983, 1992-1993, 1998/1999 Early Nieman Scholar Materials (Box 1)
- Early Nieman Materials (Box 2)
- Nieman Materials, 1992-1997 (Box 3)
- Nieman – Trips to Korea and Panama, 1996 (Box 4)
- Nieman, 1985-1988 (Box 5)
- 1978-1985 (Box 6)
- 1959-1978 (Box 7)
- Atlanta Constitution, 1988-1989 (Box 8)
- Atlanta Constitution –Memos, 1987-1988 (Box 9)
- Leaving Harvard, 1988-1989 (Box 10)
- 1990s-2000s (Box 11)
- 2000s –CCJ Materials 2005 (Box 12)
- 2000s –CCJ Materials (Box 13)
- 2000s –CCJ Materials (Box 14)
- 2000s –CCJ Materials (Box 15)
- Book Drafts –CCJ –Book Research (Box 16)
- Speeches, Writings, Jack Kelley Investigation (Box 17)
- Memoirs –Drafts of Book (Box 18)
- AV Materials (Box 19)